time2saveworkshops.com 2015-06-13

# Privacy Policy - Time 2 Save Workshops

Privacy Policy for www.time2saveworkshops.com 

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at time2save@hotmail.com. 

At www.time2saveworkshops.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.time2saveworkshops.com and how it is used. 

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.time2saveworkshops.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.time2saveworkshops.com does not use cookies. 

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.time2saveworkshops.com.

.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to www.time2saveworkshops.com and other sites on the Internet. 

.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html
